I got to be honest, I don't even
know where to begin. All I know is
that right now I have so many
thoughts swimming through my head
and I feel
very groundless. And I feel alone.
Of course, you know, I claim to
have these tools, which
I'm doing. But I don't know, I
don't know if it's plateau or what.
Or maybe the challenge
is rising on me and getting too big
for me to handle. There's a quality
to all of this
that feels unjust. And that's
probably the thing I have the
hardest time reconciling
is that my whole life I've done
nothing but try to be good and not
upset anyone.
Unfortunately, that was the way of
being that I learned as a child.
And unfortunately, I
wasn't living my pattern, routine
way of being. I don't know what you
want to call it.
Maybe another thought and I know
this is going to all me. Well, some
of it may come across
as just like a random splatter of
things. But I've wanted to, I've
wanted to do this
video recording thing for some time
and be honest, I'm kind of afraid
of doing it. Um,
it's weird. I wish I had done it
because I would love now to look
back at where my head
was at last year on this day. And
the year before that, it'd be
interesting to see any
different made any kind of progress
at all. I've been listening to some
interesting books
and taking away some insights that
I don't know. Helping me to frame
things perspective.
There's these long gaps. I keep
staring because I'm not sure. Not
sure about myself. Like
I said, I am, I'm kind of bummed
that I hadn't do these a long time
ago for the benefit of
being able to see myself. But I'm
simultaneously like incredibly, I
guess you'd say private.
Like I don't go around blathering
on about my life to other people.
Anyway, the fact
that I'm even talking or video
recording and doing this and trying
to speak a little bit
about myself is amazing in and of
itself. In fact, I think what I'll
do that I have
this looking at it's like six
minutes now, six and a half. So I
think what I'd like to
do is record again, but maybe be a
little more organized. Maybe have
my thoughts written
down. Who knows? One thing I do
know, I'm one day at a time. There
are a lot of days
where I honestly don't think I'm
going to see the sunshine tomorrow.
There's something
enormous about the pain that I'm
carrying. It's more painful than
anything I've ever
experienced in my life. Worse than
the feeling is more intense than
memories of childhood
trauma. This is, it's weird to be
like in the middle of this
experience. And I don't
know, it's hard to put it in words.
Going in and out of being able to
put my thoughts
together clearly. The one other
thing I can say is that the
cognitive load of this, like
this stress and at the same time,
starting a new job and trying to
deliver and perform
and show you the right person for
the job. That and yeah, today was
the first day of
hearing out my shit. I am listening
to a very good book. It's giving me
some insights. So
I guess tomorrow I'll continue with
the moving. They're backing and do
some work, meditate.
I don't wake up crying. It's almost
become like peeing the bed when I
was a kid. I wake
up every morning crying and no
memory of any kind of dreaming or
any anything. I go to
bed sad, I wake up sad. Been that
way for years now. So there you
have it, a 10 minute
report. Talk to you tomorrow.